{"test_questions": [[{"question": "With which type of SQL Server recovery model are all database changes logged except those that cause large log entries?", "opta": "Differential recovery", "optb": "Full recovery", "optc": "Simple recovery", "optd": "Bulk-logged recovery", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Using SQL Server 2000, which of the following symbols is used to indicate parameters in stored procedures?", "opta": "#", "optb": "%", "optc": "&", "optd": "@", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What mode of authentication does SQL Server NOT provide?", "opta": "Windows-only security", "optb": "Both SQL Server and Windows-only security", "optc": "Mixed security", "optd": "SQL Server only security", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The strictest transaction isolation level provided by SQL Server is called:", "opta": "REPEATABLE READ.", "optb": "SERIALIZABLE.", "optc": "READ COMMITTED.", "optd": "READ UNCOMMITTED.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "SQL Server program code that is executed instead of an SQL command that needs to be processed is called a(n):", "opta": "INSTEAD OF trigger.", "optb": "BEFORE trigger.", "optc": "AFTER trigger.", "optd": "BEGIN trigger.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which type of SQL Server cursor concurrency places an update lock on a row when the row is read?", "opta": "READ_ONLY", "optb": "SCROLL_LOCK", "optc": "OPTIMISTIC", "optd": "READCOMMITTED", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the three possible types of triggers does SQL Server support?", "opta": "INSTEAD OF only", "optb": "AFTER only", "optc": "BEFORE only", "optd": "INSTEAD OF and AFTER only", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is a way to create and modify tables using SQL Server?", "opta": "Write SQL code using either CREATE or ALTER SQL statements only.", "optb": "Use the graphical facilities of SQL Server Enterprise Manager only.", "optc": "Both of the two methods above will work.", "optd": "Neither of the two methods above will work.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "With which type of SQL Server recovery model, is no logging done?", "opta": "Differential recovery", "optb": "Full recovery", "optc": "Bulk-logged recovery", "optd": "Simple recovery", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "SQL Server 2000 stored procedures can:", "opta": "never be kept within the database.", "optb": "be kept within the database and invoked by application programs.", "optc": "be stored on the users' computer.", "optd": "support BEFORE, INSTEAD OF and AFTER types.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "With this type of SQL Server cursor concurrency no lock is obtained until the user updates the data.", "opta": "READ_ONLY", "optb": "SCROLL_LOCK", "optc": "OPTIMISTIC", "optd": "PESSIMISTIC", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An SQL Server 2000 language that adds programming elements like parameters, variables, IF, WHILE loops, and so forth, to the basic capabilities of SQL is called:", "opta": "COBOL.", "optb": "VB.NET.", "optc": "TRANSACT SQL.", "optd": "Visual Basic.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "With this type of index, the data are stored in the bottom level of the index and in the same order as that index.", "opta": "Nonclustered", "optb": "Clustered", "optc": "Primary", "optd": "Secondary", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In SQL Server 2000, which of the following makes a copy of the changes that have been made to the database since the last complete backup?", "opta": "Complete backup", "optb": "Transaction Log", "optc": "Differential backup", "optd": "None of the above is correct.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "With this type of index, the bottom level of an index does not contain data, but rather it contains pointers to data.", "opta": "Nonclustered", "optb": "Clustered", "optc": "Primary", "optd": "Secondary", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "With which type of SQL Server recovery model are all database changes logged?", "opta": "Differential recovery", "optb": "Full recovery", "optc": "Simple recovery", "optd": "Bulk-logged recovery", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "SQL Server automatically creates an index on:", "opta": "primary keys only.", "optb": "foreign key only.", "optc": "both primary and foreign keys.", "optd": "SQL Server never automatically creates an index.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is not a factor in determining the concurrency control behavior of SQL Server?", "opta": "Lock level", "optb": "Transaction isolation level", "optc": "Cursor concurrency setting", "optd": "Locking hints", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "SQL Server program code that is executed after an SQL command has been processed is called a(n):", "opta": "INSTEAD OF trigger.", "optb": "BEFORE trigger.", "optc": "AFTER trigger.", "optd": "BEGIN trigger.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following refers to the SQL Server transaction isolation level which places and holds locks on all rows that are read?", "opta": "REPEATABLE READ", "optb": "SERIALIZABLE", "optc": "READ COMMITTED", "optd": "READ UNCOMMITTED", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}